<song xmlns="http://openlines.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedDate="2019-08-18T13:49+04:00">
	<properties>
		<titles>
			<title>If Jesus Had Not Come</title>
		</titles>
		<authors>
			<author>Albert C. Norton</author>
		</authors>
		<copyright>© 1953 Hope Publishing Co.</copyright>
		<ccliNo>269297</ccliNo>
		<released></released>
		<key></key>
		<themes><theme>Christ: Advent and Birth</theme><theme> Christ: Life and Ministry</theme></themes>
		<songbooks>
			<songbook name="Favorite Hymns of Praise" entry="368"/>
		</songbooks>
	</properties>
	<lyrics>
		<verse name="v1">
			<lines>If Jesus had not come, how dark had been the night!
The wise men, sadly dumb, had seen no starry light!
The shepherds on the hill had heard no angel song!
The bells in silence chill, no joyous peal had rung!</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="c">
		<lines>But Jesus came! He came to earth,
And men beheld His manger birth!
The shepherds heard the angels sing,
The wise proclaimed Him Lord and King!
He died, He rose; and by His blood,
We too become the sons of God;
We preach the gospel in His name!
For Jesus came! Yes, Jesus came!</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v2">
			<lines>If Jesus had not come, no freedom had the slave;
No woman's happy home, no hand a child to save;
The people in the gloom had one eternal night:
Death met them at the tomb, no resurrection light! </lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v3">
			<lines>If Jesus had not come, no Great Physician king
Had brought a healing balm, a vision for the blind!
No soul with demon torn had found a sure release!
The hopeless and forlorn had found no way of peace! </lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v4">
			<lines>If Jesus had not come, how blank the Sacred page!
The poet had no song, and silent were the sage!
No artist to adorn our worship with delight;
No choral Psalm had borne His praises day or night! </lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v5">
			<lines>If Jesus had not come, how sad had been our fate!
Of judgment sore the sum for all our sin and hate!
No loving God of grace His precious Son had giv'n;
No hope to see His face; no joy to meet in heaven! </lines>
		</verse>
	</lyrics>
</song>