<song xmlns="http://openlines.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedDate="2019-08-18T14:01+04:00">
	<properties>
		<titles>
			<title>The Star-Spangled Banner</title>
		</titles>
		<authors>
			<author>Francis Scott Key</author>
		</authors>
		<copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
		<ccliNo>93786</ccliNo>
		<released></released>
		<key></key>
		<themes><theme>National</theme></themes>
		<songbooks>
			<songbook name="Favorite Hymns of Praise" entry="451"/>
		</songbooks>
	</properties>
	<lyrics>
		<verse name="v1">
			<lines>Oh, say can you see, by the dawn's early light,
What so proudly we hailed at the twilight's last gleaming?
Whose broad stripes and bright stars, thro' the perilous fight,
O'er the ramparts we watched, were so gallantly streaming?
And the rockets' red glare, the bombs bursting in air,
Gave proof thro' the night that our flag was still there.
Oh, say, does the star-spangled banner yet wave
O'er the land of the free, and the home of the brave?</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v2">
			<lines>On the shore, dimly seen thro' the mists of the deep,
Where the foe's haughty host in dead silence reposes,
What is that which the breeze, o'er the towering steep,
As it fitfully blows, half conceals, half discloses?
Now it catches the gleam of the morning's first beam,
In full glory reflected now shines on the stream:
'Tis the star-spangled banner; oh long may it wave
O'er the land of the free, and the home of the brave!</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v3">
			<lines>And where is that band, who so vauntingly swore
That the havoc of war and the battle's confusion,
A home and a country should leave us no more?
Their blood has washed out their foul footsteps' pollution;
No refuge could save the hireling and slave
From the terror of flight or the gloom of the grave.
And the star-spangled banner in triumph doth wave
O'er the land of the free, and the home of the brave.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v4">
			<lines>Oh, thus be it ever when free men shall stand
Between their loved homes and the war's desolation;
Blest with vict'ry and peace, may the Heav'n-rescued land
Praise the Pow'r that hath made and preserved us a nation!
Then conquer we must, when our cause it is just,
And this be our motto: "In God is our trust!"
And the star-spangled banner in triumph shall wave
O'er the land of the free and the home of the brave.</lines>
		</verse>
	</lyrics>
</song>