<song xmlns="http://openlines.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedDate="2019-08-18T16:43+04:00">
	<properties>
		<titles>
			<title>Trust</title>
		</titles>
		<authors>
			<author>Rebecca N. Taylor (bef.1883)</author>
			<author>Rebecca N. Taylor (pub.1915; alt.)</author>
		</authors>
		<copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
		<ccliNo>5399000</ccliNo>
		<released></released>
		<key></key>
		<songbooks>
			<songbook name="50 Uncommon Songs" entry="40"/>
		</songbooks>
		<comments>
			<comment>Psalm 18:2</comment>
		</comments>
	</properties>
	<lyrics>
		<verse name="v1">
			<lines>Though the rain may fall and the wind be blowing,
And cold and chill is the wintry blast;
Though the cloudy sky is still cloudier growing,
And dead leaves tell that the summer has passed,
Yet my face I hold to the stormy heaven,
My heart as calm as a summer sea;
I am glad to receive what my God hath given,
Whate’er it be.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v2">
			<lines>When I feel the cold, I can say, “He sends it,”
His wind blows blessing I surely know;
For I’ve ne’er a want but that He attends it;
My heart beats warm, though the winds may blow;
The soft, sweet summer was warm and glowing,
So bright were the blossoms on every bough;
I trusted Him when the roses were blowing—
I trust Him now.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v3">
			<lines>Oh, small were my faith should it weakly falter,
When now the roses have ceased to blow;
And frail were the trust that now should alter,
To doubt His love when the storm clouds grow;
If I trust Him once I must trust Him ever—
His way is best, though I stand or fall;
Through wind or storm He will leave me never,
For He sends all.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v4">
			<lines>Now why should my heart be faint and fearing?
The Mighty One rules above the storm;
For even the wintry blast is cheering,
Revealing His power to keep me warm;
No, never a care on my heart is pressing,
And never a fear can disturb my breast;
Yes, everything that He sends is blessing,
For He knows best.</lines>
		</verse>
	</lyrics>
</song>