<song xmlns="http://openlines.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedIn="Hymnary.org Scrapper 0.0.1" modifiedDate="2019-08-18T16:43+04:00">
	<properties>
		<titles>
			<title>Unanswered Yet</title>
		</titles>
		<authors>
			<author>Charles D. Tillman (pub.1883)</author>
			<author>Unknown (pub.1912)</author>
		</authors>
		<copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
		<ccliNo></ccliNo>
		<released></released>
		<key></key>
		<songbooks>
			<songbook name="50 Uncommon Songs" entry="41"/>
		</songbooks>
		<comments>
			<comment>Psalm 143:1; Luke 18:1</comment>
			<comment>Could not find CCLI number.</comment>
		</comments>
	</properties>
	<lyrics>
		<verse name="v1">
			<lines>Unanswered yet? The prayer your lips have pleaded
In agony of heart these many years?
Does faith begin to fail, is hope departing,
And think you all in vain those falling tears?
Say not the Father hath not heard your prayer;
You shall have your desire, sometime, somewhere.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v2">
			<lines>Unanswered yet? Though when you first presented
This one petition at the Father’s throne,
It seemed you could not wait the time of asking,
So urgent was your heart to make it known.
Though years have passed since then, do not despair;
The Lord will answer you, sometime, somewhere.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v3">
			<lines>Unanswered yet? But you are not unheeded;
The promises of God forever stand;
To Him our days and years alike are equal;
“Have faith in God”; it is your Lord’s command.
Hold on to Jacob’s angel and your prayer
Shall bring a blessing down sometime, somewhere.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v4">
			<lines>Unanswered yet? Nay, do not say ungranted;
Perhaps your part is not yet wholly done;
The work began when first your prayer was uttered,
And God will finish what He has begun.
If you will keep the incense burning there,
His glory you shall see, sometime, somewhere.</lines>
		</verse>
		<verse name="v5">
			<lines>Unanswered yet? Faith cannot be unanswered;
Her feet were firmly planted on the Rock;
Amid the wildest storm prayer stands undaunted,
Nor quails before the loudest thunder shock.
She knows Omnipotence has heard her prayer,
And cries, “It shall be done,” sometime, somewhere.</lines>
		</verse>
	</lyrics>
</song>